animalrights.net 2000-03-05

# Animal Rights Net - Privacy Statement

**Home**   
**  
Bookstore  
** **  
Discussion Forums  
****  
Links  
****  
News Headlines  
**[**  
Newsletter  
**](http://www.animalrights.net/ar_newsletter.html)**  
Privacy Statement  
****  
Search  
****  
What's New?** **  
******

* * *

**AnimalRights.Net Weekly Poll**  

## Privacy Statement for Animal Rights.Net

Carnell.Com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: **AnimalRights.Net**. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We use cookies on our discussion forums and in the online polls to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, and for other purposes. 

Our site's discussion forum registration form gives users the option of giving us contact information (such as their name and email address). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

This site contains links to other sites. **AnimalRights.Net** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

We occasionally run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (such as their email address). The customer's contact information is used only to contact the visitor with results of the specific contest. No data gathered from such contests will be used for any further promotional uses. 

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

## Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

If you are receiving communications from this site and would like to opt yout, you should send email to [brian@carnell.com](mailto:brian@carnell.com)

## Correct/Update

In order to change and/or modify information previously provided please email [brian@carnell.com](mailto:brian@carnell.com)

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact Brian Carnell [Carnell.Com](http://www.carnell.com/) [brian@carnell.com](mailto:brian@carnell.com)
**Home**   
  
**Bookstore** **  
**  
**Discussion Forums **

**Links**

**News Headlines  
****  
Newsletter** **  
**  
**Privacy Statement** **** **Search** **  
**   
**What's New?**

* * *

**AnimalRights.Net Weekly Poll**  

## Privacy Statement for Animal Rights.Net

       Carnell.Com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: **AnimalRights.Net**. 

       We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We use cookies on our discussion forums and in the online polls to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, and for other purposes. 

       Our site's discussion forum registration form gives users the option of giving us contact information (such as their name and email address). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

       This site contains links to other sites. **AnimalRights.Net** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

        We occasionally run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (such as their email address). The customer's contact information is used only to contact the visitor with results of the specific contest. No data gathered from such contests will be used for any further promotional uses. 

       We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

## Public Forums

       This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

## Security

       This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

## Choice/Opt-Out

       Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

       This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

       If you are receiving communications from this site and would like to opt yout, you should send email to [brian@carnell.com](mailto:brian@carnell.com)

## Correct/Update

       In order to change and/or modify information previously provided please email [brian@carnell.com](mailto:brian@carnell.com)

## Contacting the Web Site

       If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact 

Brian Carnell  
[Carnell.Com  
](http://www.carnell.com/) [brian@carnell.com](mailto:brian@carnell.com)
